So friends, finally ICICI LBAT General
Insurance Company has disclosed its Quarter 4
numbers.  The company has also announced a final dividend of
₹7 per equity share for its shareholders
and the record date
and payment date related to this will be
announced by the company in the upcoming AGM.  The
company has told us this here.
Now let us see what kind of
actual numbers of the company we are
seeing.
So friends, we have come to the company
numbers.  The data is given to us in these lax.
We will discuss it in crores.
So see, the total income of the company for this quarter has been Rs
crore.  In the last quarter it was ₹610 crore
and last year the company had generated income of ₹5851 crore.
So the income has increased on yearly basis.
We are also getting good income growth on quarterly basis.  Let's talk about the
net premium income of the company.  So see
here the net premium income of the company has been Rs
5790 crore.  In the previous quarter it
was Rs 5685 crore and last year the
company had earned net premium income of Rs 5225 crore.
So we are also seeing the yearly quarterly premium income
increasing which is a
good thing.  Let's talk about the company's
expenses, friends.  So see, the company's expenses for this quarter were Rs
672 crore.
In the last quarter it was Rs 639 crore and last year the
company had spent Rs 5435 crore.
Yearly expenses increased.
We are finding the quarterly company expenses manageable.  Let's
talk about the net profit of the company.
So friends, the company's profit for this quarter
is Rs 546 crore.  In the last quarter it
was Rs 658 crore and last year the
company had generated a profit of Rs 59 crore.  So, on yearly
basis, profit has increased, but on
quarterly basis, we are
seeing a decline in profit.  Talking about the
EPS of the company, so friends, the EPS of the company
that is being seen for this quarter is
₹10.97.  Last quarter was ₹13.25
and last year the company generated EPS of ₹10.29.
So EPS has
increased on yearly basis.  We are also seeing a decline in EPS on quarterly basis
and the
company has
not provided information on other things like NPS etc.  So
friends, these were the numbers of ICICI Piden Life Insurance sorry
General Insurance for quarter 4.   I
hope you liked the video.
If you liked the video, please like it
and subscribe to the channel for more such updates.
Thank you.